I'm sure no one would believe it.
Nice to meet you, members
of the council of elders.
My name is Subaru Natsuki.
I am a manservant in Roswaal's mansion,
and I serve as this candidate's...
Lady Emilia's best knight!
I ain't got no name to give.
I'm just...
a stick swinger.
The hell's your deal?
Throwin' a sword at me?
You got a death wish?
To attack an unarmed man is an act
that would disgrace any knight.
Hah! Don't make me laugh!
I hope you do not
come to regret those words!
You thought I was unarmed?
Look closer.
Wooden... sticks?
No, you idiot. They're chopsticks.
I keep 'em on me in case
I need a little snack.
If I swing 'em just the right way,
at just the right angle and
just the right speed...
there's nothing I can't cut
through, even with chopsticks!
Julius!
Jiwaldo!
My sword can even
cut through light, y'know!
Jiwaldo!
Jiwaldo! Jiwaldo!
You gotta aim better!
You'll never get your
pretty boy back that way!
Jiwaldo! Jiwaldo! Jiwaldo!
Jiwaldo! Jiwaldo!
Lady Anastasia!
That's enough!
Jiwal...
Lady Anastasia!
You're just my kinda guy right now!
You're gettin' me excited!
Move aside!
The hell is this?
Don't make me laugh, man.
If this is the best ya got,
you're a real disappointment.
You're boring me!
I am...
If you wanna get to that
woman, I'll let ya go.
Crawl into her nice, soft lap
to cry and beg for attention,
you ugly, useless excuse for a knight!
Take a nap.
Now...
who's next?
I'd just like to ask one question.
Didn't we just need to
make you move one step?
You were running around lots.
Don't take that at face value.
I just said it to sound cool.
You get it, don't ya?
I guess not, you bein' a woman and all.
A real hottie, too. You
should go out with me.
I'm sorry. I don't understand
what you're saying.
Also, I don't think I
could beat you in a fight.
E-Emilia?
You seem very strong.
I could see that by watching you.
But we have to get past this exam.
So please give us a way to win.
If I can make you take
even one step, we win.
That'll be our contest.
No?
Damn, nice! I actually don't hate that!
You're the biggest idiot
I've seen since Tricia!
I like you!
Fine. If you make me take
one step, you win.
Take care of the two of them.
H-Hang on! You saw him just now!
You need a plan for—
Icebrand Arts.
Icicle Line.
Don't worry.
I'll take this seriously, too.
You're pretty stubborn for such a hottie.
I do what I can, the best I can.
That's how I learned to do
things... from my knight!
They're both all right, I suppose. But...
I know.
He's not moving.
You're open!
Wha—
Perks of fighting a hottie.
Don't get mad over a little thing like—
Ow!
Wh-What the hell are you thinkin'?!
Most chicks would lose their edge
after bein' touched like that!
Huh? But all you did was touch me.
I mean, you were wide open.
Oh, screw you! How the hell
were you brought up, anyway?!
What were your parents thinkin'?!
Did I say something strange?
Yo! Do somethin' about this woman!
Don't let her go outside!
You're her attendant, aren't ya?!
Screw you, you prick!
What are you trying to pull?!
You pervert! Shitbag! Sin Archbishop!
I will end you!
Subaru! Calm down!
I understand how you feel,
but look, I suppose!
He moved! And more than just one step!
Oh! You're right!
I did it! I won!
A win is a win, no matter how it happened.
So what now?
Well, that's how it goes.
I said what I said.
Wait, you're admitting it?
Just who the hell do you think I am?
If I refuse to back down now,
it's just gonna make me look bad.
After the way you just lost,
you couldn't look any worse.
Shut yer trap, wuss!
Anyway, the hottie wins.
I'll let you pass.
It is what it is.
Well? Is the wuss gonna do the next one?
Or is it gonna be one of the two brats?
There are seven inside the tower.
Your woman here is the
first one to make it out.
Huh?
So who's gonna be next to get past me?
Well, bro?
So you came running back dejected?
Harsh, Big Sister.
Stop talking like that.
You'll make that sleeping girl's story
about you being her master feel real.
Yikes, wouldn't want that.
I'll be careful.
So it was a crushing defeat.
Only Lady Emilia could measure up to him.
Yes, I won.
Maybe I should go up alone?
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
It's, well... you know... dangerous.
I'll be very careful.
Dangerous.
Dangerous indeed.
I just hope Julius isn't feeling too down.
You're worried?
Hard to say.
I mean, sure, I'm worried about him...
but it's not that simple, you know?
Also...
why did she try so hard to help Julius?
I'm concerned for them,
but the exam is important, too.
If we don't get past it, we won't
find a way to get Rem back.
To be completely honest, that
examiner was insanely strong.
Maybe even on Reinhard's level.
Yeah. I think he was just that strong.
Right now, there's only one person
in each nation who's strong enough
to be called the best in the world.
Reinhard's the strongest in the kingdom...
so there's one like him in each
of the other three countries, too?
The top general of the Vollachia Empire,
the "Blue Lightning," Cecils Segmund.
The "Mad Prince" of the
Holy Kingdom of Gusteco.
And the city-state of Kararagi
has the "Admirer," Halibel.
None of them fit the description
of the stick swinger.
His outfit resembled the traditional
attire of Kararagi, I suppose.
He was also a master at using chopsticks.
I'm not sure you could call him a master.
That's not even how chopsticks are used.
Hey, you guys... Got a minute?
Master... Don't leave me alone...
I don't want to be lonely anymore...
Don't say sad stuff when
we're just about to leave!
You're totally awake, aren't you?
Boo.
Huh? What are you guys doing here?
Last thing I remember was Master's flash
of insight getting us past the exam...
Is this a dream?
It's real.
Well, then Master hugged me and said,
laughing, "I won't let you go again."
That's a dream!
You passed out the moment
the second exam started.
Passed out? Me?
I'd never do anything that pathetic!
You don't remember?
We went up that long stairway
and into a white room...
Uh-huh.
Then, when I pulled out the sword, the
scenery changed, and a person appeared...
Uh-huh.
A guy with red hair and blue eyes who
called himself a "stick swinger."
Ow! Ow, ow, ow! You remember now?!
Wh-Wh-What is he doing here?!
He's alive! He really is
a guy you just can't kill!
Huh?! What are you—
"Stick swinger"!
Reid the Stick Swinger!
That brute! That devil!
He came back alive just so
he could fondle my boobs!
Reid? Wasn't Reid the guy who...
Reid Astrea.
The first Sword Saint.
Julius, sorry to bug you
when you're asleep.
We figured out who that guy
was, and we need your...
That idiot!
We're not just playin'
around this time, bro.
I am Julius Juukulius of the
Lugunica Imperial Knights.
So long as you keep throwin'
around that stupid title,
you're not even worth my
time to play with.
Boring!
Playing exactly by the book, aren't ya?!
There ya go!
Hmph! Damn, you're pathetic.
How long have you been using a sword, anyway?
It's only been three
months for me, y'know.
I... will defeat you... right here and—
Don't be dumb.
You really think you can?
You can't. Not you.
You won't swing that sword enough
to reach me! You haven't yet!
You're not good enough!
This is no place for you!
You're the wrong actor for this
scene! Nobody invited you!
Nobody's watching a loser like you.
Nobody expects anything of you.
Don't get complacent thinkin'
I'm just playin' around!
Damn, you withstood that?
You're just gettin' more and more boring.
Right now...
this strength...
is the only thing I...
Your hesitation's showing in
your sword work.
You're not worthy of the heavenly sword.
You can't even manage to be a follower.
My eyes know just how strong you are!
My humiliation knows it!
No matter who else may forget!
Julius!
It's... very shaky...
Oh, you're awake?
I'm on your back?
That's right.
Just so you know, this is the
second time in not very long.
Do you know how it feels
to be doing this again
thirty minutes after saying I
never wanted to do it again?
No wonder I feel so uncomfortable.
You want me to drop you?
Will Lady Anastasia be all right?
Her life's not in danger.
You came a lot closer
to death than she did.
Up against him...
You know, you're gonna be shocked when
you find out who that eyepatch guy was.
Reid Astrea.
Good on you for knowing.
I had to learn it from Shaula.
I had a hunch the moment he called
himself a "stick swinger,"
but I couldn't be certain.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
It's fine.
Julius...
I'm gonna tell you this since you'll
find out when we get back anyway.
After you and Lady Anastasia went down,
Emilia passed the exam.
But it wasn't like she matched her
opponent in strength or anything.
She just had a lot of coincidences
line up in her favor,
plus Emilia is just...
you know... special.
So... I mean... don't get too excited.
Excited?
If Lady Emilia was able to pass the exam,
then Reid the Sword Saint is
not an insurmountable obstacle.
That knowledge alone helps us immensely.
Y-Yeah, you're right. That's true.
So long as you realize that.
Would you mind letting me down now?
I fear I'll get sick if I have
to ride on your back any longer.
Emilia would kill me if she found out
I made you walk while you're hurt.
I'm awake. I can go
down these stairs myself.
Little late for the tough act now.
Everyone already saw me
carrying you earlier.
Except Shaula and Lady Anastasia,
that is, since they were unconscious.
Then that will be my reason.
I can't let Lady Anastasia see—
Don't make it sound so forced.
Put me down.
You know, you—
I said put me down!
Whoa, hey! Hang on!
You...
You idiot! What are you even thinking?!
Stay away!
I can stand on my own.
I do not need...
your help!
I told you.
Standing up on my own is a simple matter.
I may be a bit slow, but there's no
need to put you through any trouble.
Could you go on ahead and tell
the others what happened?
I will explain things to them myself.
You need only tell them that you found me.
Oh, damn it! Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Idiots! You and I are both huge idiots!
What are you—
Shut up! You can stand
on your own, my ass!
I can plainly see how
hunched over you are!
You knew before that fight was over
that you couldn't win, didn't you?
He beat you, kicked you,
knocked you down...
and you still had no choice but
to keep going after him, right?!
There was no other way to
get it out of your system!
Thanks to a certain someone, I
understand that damn well by now!
I won't talk as if I know how
you really feel deep down.
But right now, there's no need for you
to try to get down this
long-ass stairway alone.
I can spare a shoulder for you, and
I won't even think of it as a favor.
Back then, I...
So I'm not gonna let you
go down these stairs alone!
Subaru.
What?
I'm sorry.
Shut up.
I'm sure
no one would believe it.
The blowhard who made enemies of everyone
in the castle's great hall that day...
Even the very man who said it
couldn't hide his frivolous attitude
or the fact that he was riding
on momentum when he said it.
No one...
would believe
Julius Juukulius
there was someone in that hall
who was deeply moved by that.